## Felipe Bevilacqua - 27 year old

Date of birth: 10/07/1987

Address: 1414 Mazzei Av. ap. 141

City: Sao Paulo – SP – Brazil - (I want to move and live in another country)

CEP: 02310-002

Home Phone: +55 (11) 2206-1220 Cell phone: +55 (11) 97600-4400 E-mail: contact@felipebevi.com.br

Personal Portifolio: http://en.felipebevi.com.br

### Role of interest

PHP developer systems

## Summary of Curriculum

11 years in the area, I have knowledge and experience in C, PHP and JAVA; have extensive knowledge of new tools and frameworks. I've worked with databases MySQL and SQL Server 2008, SCRUM organization; ease of working code in production management versioning in SVN / GIT, consolidated into Magento, Wordpress, jQuery, ZEND, CSS3, HTML5 and responsive design experiences. Environments Apache, Ubuntu, NGINX and Windows. Now I'm programmer in Objective C to developer Apple applications.

I want to move and live in other country because I have 2 son and I want find a better life quality for me and my family

# **Specializations**

Installation and Maintenance of microcomputers - Computer City - 3 months - 2000

English - CCAA - São Paulo - SP - 4 years - 1998 to 2002 - Conclusion

English - Wisdom - São Paulo - SP - 1 year - 2003 - Completed

PHP with MySQL - Essentials - Senac - Consolation - 30 hours - 2005 -

JavaCard - FIAP - 30 hours - 2006 - Completed

Ajax with PHP and JSP - FIAP - 16 hours - 2008 - Completed

Keep as a hobby in the Arduino development platform (C). Developing personal projects for home automation and smart products for external companies.

### Professional experience (descending order)

### CAMPANHA DIGITAL - 08/2014 until the moment

Analyst Programmer PHP

Maintenance of websites and internal company systems, social application development for IOS mirror site www.transportedecente.com.br and the creation of sites for political candidates: www.camposmachado.com.br, www.marlenesenadora.com.br, www.drmachado.com.br, www.policeneto.com.br. Using PHP with MySQL and Wordpress, as well as customization of modules, including some items as HTML5 audio in the background and integration plan with the Facebook API aa pair creating Fanpages (iframes within Facebook for the site), integrating platforms officers with social media.



#### **LEMA21 - 4 months - 03/2014 the 07/2014**

• Programmer Analyst Sr. PHP

Creation of new features and maintenance of the company www.lema21.com.br, an e-commerce site based on Magento, developing solutions NGINX with MySQL servers. Change templates in MVC structure, creating new layouts and modules and integrated into the system reports.

#### **THOMSON REUTERS - 1** year and 8 months - 04/2012 to 12/2013

• Sr. PHP Programmer Analyst - Last post - 04/2012 the 12/2013 - 1 year and 8 months

After the acquisition of FISCO Soft by Thomson Reuters had key role in the migration and conversion of data from over 10 million records from the local database to the new world system. Actively participating in daily meetings and conferences between Spain, USA and Argentina (listening and answering questions in Spanish and English). Worked on implementation of SCRUM for work and organization of the new development team. All this in 10 months to complete a product of worldwide named Checkpoint (Brazil), which is already used by all the 100 largest companies in the USA. 85% of the information of this new system, were migrated from FISCO Soft under my coordination.

# FISCO SOFT PUBLISHING LTD. - 1 year and 1 month - 03/2011 the 04/2012

- Sr. PHP Programmer Analyst Last post 06/2011 the 04/2012 10 months
   Schedule and lead the team (6 developers with PHP) in the development of daily tasks, centralize and distribute the calls of the customers and control / document the hours spent with each project within the company by programmer.
- Sr. PHP Programmer Penultimate position 03/2011 the 06/2011 3 months
   Responsible for development and maintenance of websites in PHP company. Provide ongoing
   maintenance of the site Fiscosoft.com.br and their products (Decisoes.com.br, Comexdata.com.br,
   Systax.com.br, Isstotal.com.br, prefeituraeletronica.com.br, mundocontabil.com. br,
   rotinastrabalhistas.com.br, setorialiss.com.br, guiasiscoserv.com.br, among others).

## CATHO ONLINE - 1 year - 01/2010 the 01/2011

Senior Programmer PHP Mysql - Last post - 01/2010 the 01/2011 - 1 year
 Responsible for developing new solutions and resolutions of technical problems throughout the site
 CareerBuilder and its internal systems. Among these, we highlight all the new development area subscribers and website http://cadastro.catho.com.br. Worked with SCRUM methodology and object orientation.

# INNANZI TECHNOLOGY AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS - 4 months - 06/2009 to 10/2009

Telecommunications Analyst - Last post - 06/2009 the 10/2009 - 4 months
 Management and maintenance of IPBX systems (Linux, asterisk); responsible for all the needs, requests and reports in the field of telecommunications (based on PHP and MySQL), backup routines, seeking and implementing new technologies, monitoring the data link and E1. Developing new solutions as well as integration with particular systems with front-end in PHP / MySQL.

### TELECOM AND NETWORKING FOCUS LTD - 1 year - 06/2008 the 06/2009

Analyst Developer PHP / JAVA / PERL - Last post - 06/2008 the 06/2009 - 1 year
 Updating and creating interface for Linux-based telephony system called Asterisk, enabling seamless integration and control of the system by users, as well as statistical and operational controls through functions and routines created via interface using PHP and Ajax. Creating an auto-dial system, monitoring and statistical extensions to a complete phone system reports.

# **PRIME SOLUTION -** 2 months - 04/2008 the 06/2008

• PHP Programmer Analyst - Last post - 04/2008 the 06/2008 - 2 months

Responsible for all PHP development company; contributions in the development of 80% of the site: www.valeriotrabanco.com and by tweaking the company's website.

#### IBM BRAZIL - INDUSTRIAL MACHINERY AND SERVICES - 3 months - 10/2007 to 01/2008

Java Programmer Analyst - Last post - the 01/2008 10/2007 - 3 months
 Responsible for the analysis and development of a Java-based solution that integrates with
 Mainframe; which generated daily reports of all ATMs of the ABN (Real) to Brazil level. Task performed

## OVER FLASH WEB DESIGN COMPUTER - 2 years and 6 months - 01/2005 the 07/2007

1 hour before all performed by a sector of 10 people per day.

Delphi Programmer Analyst / PHP - Last post - 01/2005 the 07/2007 - 2 years and 6 months
Responsible for 50% of creating a whole ERP system for logistics management and a module, this
same system in PHP that allows customers of these companies consult stock and deliveries in real
time via internet. I was also responsible for all financial control of the company, as well as contact
with clients and customers in system deployments.

#### DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION STATE OF SAO PAULO - 9 months - 03/2004 to 12/2004

Web Designer - Last post - 03/2004 the 12/2004 - 9 months
 Initiated the development of the Secretariat sites, earning that year a contest to design the best government websites; I was responsible for 100% of website development www.drhu.sp.gov.br and after this experience, I dedicated myself to experience in support of the Secretariat. Being responsible for the technical and called attention to employees.

## **Training**

Undergraduate #1

Institution: FIAP - Faculty of Informatics and Adm Paulista.

Training level: Undergraduate Course Name: Information Systems

Current year: already formed

Start date: 01/2005

Completion date: 12/2008

Undergraduate # 2

Institution: Senac

Degree of training: Technician
Course Name: Computer Technician

Current year: already formed

Start date: 01/2003

Date of completion: 09/2004

Extracurricular # 1

Institution: IMPACTA Technology Degree of training: Technician Course name: iOS Development

Current year: Studying Start date: 06/2014

Expected date of completion: 12/2014